[UPBEAT MUSIC]
♪ YOU THINK I'M PRETTY
WITHOUT ANY MAKEUP ON ♪
♪ YOU THINK I'M FUNNY WHEN I
TELL THE PUNCH LINE WRONG ♪
♪ I KNOW YOU GET ME, SO I
LET MY WALLS COME DOWN ♪
♪ DOWN ♪
♪ BEFORE YOU MET ME
I WAS ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ BUT THINGS WERE KINDA HEAVY ♪
♪ YOU BROUGHT ME TO LIFE ♪
♪ NOW EVERY FEBRUARY ♪
♪ YOU'LL BE MY VALENTINE ♪
♪ VALENTINE ♪
♪ LET'S GO ALL THE WAY TONIGHT ♪
♪ NO REGRETS, JUST LOVE ♪
♪ WE CAN DANCE UNTIL WE DIE ♪
♪ YOU AND I WILL
BE YOUNG FOREVER ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME ♪
♪ FEEL LIKE I'M LIVING
A TEENAGE DREAM ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU TURN ME ON ♪
♪ I CAN'T SLEEP ♪
♪ LET'S RUN AWAY AND
DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ MY HEART STOPS ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOOK AT ME ♪
♪ JUST ONE TOUCH ♪
♪ NOW BABY, I BELIEVE
THIS IS REAL ♪
♪ SO TAKE A CHANCE AND
DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ WE DROVE TO CALI AND
GOT DRUNK ON THE BEACH ♪
♪ GOT A MOTEL AND BUILT
A FORT OUT OF SHEETS ♪
♪ I FINALLY FOUND YOU,
MY MISSING PUZZLE PIECE ♪
♪ I'M COMPLETE ♪
♪ LET'S GO ALL THE WAY TONIGHT ♪
♪ NO REGRETS, JUST LOVE ♪
♪ WE CAN DANCE UNTIL WE DIE ♪
♪ YOU AND I WILL
BE YOUNG FOREVER ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME ♪
♪ FEEL LIKE I'M LIVING
A TEENAGE DREAM ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU TURN ME ON ♪
♪ I CAN'T SLEEP ♪
♪ LET'S RUN AWAY AND
DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ MY HEART STOPS ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOOK AT ME ♪
♪ JUST ONE TOUCH ♪
♪ NOW BABY, I BELIEVE
THIS IS REAL ♪
♪ SO TAKE A CHANCE AND
DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ I'MA GET YOUR HEART RACING
IN MY SKIN-TIGHT JEANS ♪
♪ BE YOUR TEENAGE
DREAM TONIGHT ♪
♪ LET YOU PUT YOUR HANDS ON
ME IN MY SKIN-TIGHT JEANS ♪
♪ BE YOUR TEENAGE
DREAM TONIGHT ♪
♪ TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT,
TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME ♪
♪ FEEL LIKE I'M LIVING
A TEENAGE DREAM ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU TURN ME ON ♪
♪ I CAN'T SLEEP ♪
♪ LET'S RUN AWAY AND
DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ NO ♪
♪ MY HEART STOPS ♪
♪ WHEN YOU LOOK AT ME ♪
♪ JUST ONE TOUCH ♪
♪ NOW BABY, I BELIEVE
THIS IS REAL ♪
♪ SO TAKE A CHANCE AND
DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ DON'T EVER LOOK BACK ♪
♪ I'MA GET YOUR HEART RACING
IN MY SKIN-TIGHT JEANS ♪
♪ BE YOUR TEENAGE
DREAM TONIGHT ♪
♪ LET YOU PUT YOUR HANDS ON
ME IN MY SKIN-TIGHT JEANS ♪
♪ BE YOUR TEENAGE
DREAM TONIGHT ♪
♪ TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT,
TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT ♪